

Md. Perves Hossen

Full-stack Web Developer

Education

2018 - Running BBA in Marketing National University

2016 - 2018 H.S.C Dania University College

2014 - 2016 S.S.C Muradpur Samiran Nessa High School

Contact

Phone +880 1997 015981

Email developer.perves@gmail.com

Address 126, Muradpur Madrasha road, Kadamtali, Dhaka-1204

Profile

Hello, everyone. I'm Md. Perves a professional Full-Stack Web Developer. Style & Develop is my passion. I have 3+ years of working experience in both local & international designing industries having advanced knowledge of full-Stack website developer with expertise in PHP, Laravel, MySQL database, React.js, Firebase, Node.js, MongoDB, Express.js, Rest API, Html, CSS, Bootstrap, JAVASCRIPT, JQUERY & Ajax.

Experience

2020 - Present Full Stack Web developer
Future Innovation LTD Hollo Lworking boro go g

Hello, I working here as a Full stack web developer and a team leader. I am working here more than 2 years.

2019 - Present Fiverr Inc. Web Design & Development

Hello there, I am working as a

Freelancer for last 3 year and I am a

level One seller Here.

Skills

HTML & CSS		LARAVEL	
JAVASCIPT		PHP	••••
REACT.JS		NODE.JS	••••
MYSQL	••••	MONGODB	••••